

YOVIE ALFAGUISTUTA

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I am 23 years old and I am a web developer who graduated in 2021. Coding on **React JS** and **Laravel** with **2+ years** of experience. I Already serve several clients to build web based applications. My greatest strength in technical terms is problem solving and logical thinking. I am also very enthusiastic and interested to use or learn new things.

SOFT SKILL

- Problem Solving
- Logical Thinking
- Creativty
- Time Management
- Teamwork

TECH STACK

- React JS
- Laravel





PROGRAMMING TOOLS

Jest

Sentry

Linux

Pgsql & Mysql

- Github & Gitlab
- Docker & PM2
- Go Fiber
- CI / CD (Jenkins)
- Postman & Swagger

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 Bachelor degree S1 Informatika (S.Kom)

at Universitas Teknokrat Indonesia,

GPA 3,45.

High school graduate from SMAN 2015 - 2017

5 Bandar Lampung, Science Major

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Microdata Indonesia 2020 - 2022

Create, debug, test, analytze and modify more than 20+ complex apps from start to production

Web Developer Freelance 2020 - 2022

Develop more than 10+ variant application and system for thesis

Internship Android Developer BAPPEDA (Intern) 2020

Developing 2 Android Mobile Apps for Government activities within 2 months of work

LANGUAGE

Indonesia

English



yoviealfaguistuta@gmail.com



My Site http://yoviealfaguistuta.site



Address

Pulau Sanama Street, Bandar Lampung

